Mezzo Pollo, Mezzo Pollo!
Half a feather, twice the flight!
Mezzo Pollo, co-co-cocò!
Half of me, but all the flow!
[Instrumental]
Look at my beak, look at my feather!
I race along like foam!
Three lanes of pure madness!
I jump left and fly away!
I grab half a cookie.
I'm a plush toy, but I'm not cooked!
I slide across pink pudding.
This race is fabulous!
Mezzo Pollo, Mezzo Pollo!
Half a feather, twice the flight!
Mezzo Pollo, co-co-cocò!
Half of me, but all the flow!
This way, that way!
Pick only half!
If a whole chicken appears...
[Chopped vocals over the beat]
The arrow points right,
but opposites make the rules!
I head left and turn my beak.
I do a jerky little dance!
Half of "LUNA" becomes "LU"!
Co-co-cocò, you say it too!
Not cooked! I'm on the track
in my surfer's puffer jacket!
Mezzo Pollo, Mezzo Pollo!
Half a feather, twice the flight!
Mezzo Pollo, co-co-cocò!
Half of me, but all the flow!
This way, that way!
Pick only half!
If a whole chicken appears...
WHOLE CHICKEN!
Freeze! Freeze!
Be a statue!
Beak to the sky!
One, two...
Don't say "dunno"!
Three, off you go!
Co-co-cocò!
Mezzo Pollo, Mezzo Pollo!
Half a feather, twice the flight!
Mezzo Pollo, co-co-cocò!
Half of me, but all the flow!
This way, that way!
Pick only half!
If a whole chicken appears...
Mezzo Pollo, Mezzo Pollo!
Half a feather, twice the flight!
Mezzo Pollo, co-co-cocò!
Half of me, but all the flow!
Mezzo Pollo in my brain,
the chorus goes around again!
Co-co-cocò!
Shall I start again, or not?
[Instrumental outro]